http://www.bambach.co.uk/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
We (Bambach UK) regard your privacy as important. In this Privacy Notice we will explain how we collect your information, what we do with it and what rights you are afforded under Data Protection regulations to amend, correct and delete that information.
This website does not automatically capture or store personal information, other than information that is automatically logged about visitors and which is used to produce statistics on the use of the site. The following types of information are automatically collected and stored about visits:
GEO locations of visitors used to access the site (NOT individual IP addresses).
Internet browser and operating system statistics of computers used to access the site.
Date and times of visits to the site.
Pages visited on the site.
Referral web addresses, for visits from other web sites.
Address of search engines and search terms used, for visits from search engines.
IMPORTANT NOTE: We have no way of tracking this information back to you as an individual, nor do we collect or analyse web visitor statistics about individuals. Information is used for generalised statistics only, so we can evaluate website use, in order to improve our services to our web visitors.
This information is collected by our web server using cookies. If you disable cookies in your browser settings you may experience problems using this or other websites. For example, our system will not be able to remember your email address for future visits and may have problems processing your order. In order to reliably turn off tracking, you will need to use the ‘Do Not Track’ settings in modern browsers such as Firefox 4, Internet Explorer 9 or Chrome. You may need to speak to your IT administrator to configure this.
This website does not store any passwords, payment/credit/debit card details or other customer details using cookies.
We are required by the General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR) to inform you of your rights regarding any information you have provided to us. Information we collect from you, where you choose to provide it to us, enables us to provide you information about products and services in which you register an interest.
You may be asked for personal information if you wish to use our services, such as placing an order for goods, requesting a printed catalogue, setting up an account, requesting services including newsletters, web forums, assessment & consultative services etc, or if you make a general enquiry or ask us to contact you.
By your action of providing this information, you are providing us with positive consent to collect this information. We will use this information to manage any account, personalise your use of the website or provide any service you have requested from us. In each case we will only use the personal information you provide to service the request you have made to us. You have specific rights regarding the personal information we have collected from you and these rights are:
The right to be informed
The right of access
The right to rectification
The right to erasure
The right to restrict processing
The right to data portability
The right to object
Rights in relation to automated decision making and profiling
In relation to (1) above, this Privacy Notice provides you with your right to be informed.
In relation to your rights (2) through to (7) inclusive, please contact us via our Contact Us page, highlighting your query is regarding data in the comments box, or contact our Adminstration Team on 020 8532 5100.
In relation to (8), we do not perform any automated decision making and profiling.
We have in place technical measures to protect your PI, multi-level firewalls, AES256 encrypted databases, physical and logical access controls, Role Based Access Controls (RBAC) with least privilege used, no shared accounts and multi-factor logins. Our Cloud service provision uses a state of the art facility with 24hr guards, CCTV, physical and biometric access controls and other undisclosed systems.
All our data (including yours) is housed within the EU, backed up in the UK and is NOT exported outside the EU. We do not share or disclose your PI with any other party unless instructed to by you or your organisation.
Links within this site to other websites outside of this organisation are not covered by this policy.
Contact
Bambach UK4 Northgate Business CentreCrown Road Enfield, LondonEN1 1TG
© The Bambach Saddle Seat (Europe) Ltd 2018 all rights reserved
{{ model.symbol() }}{{ model.value | number:2 }}
{{ model.quantity }}
Web design by Webfuel Ltd
SEARCH
